Noor Yulita Apsari

Kudus 59319 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/noor-yulita-apsari/ | 0895384826016 | nooryulitaapsari@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am a third-year student studying Informatics Engineering at Universitas Negeri Semarang. My main interest in programming has been in Web Programming, UI Design, and Data Analyst. I am a person that is constantly growing and expanding my abilities. I have good time management skills and can work well in a group or on my own.

EXPERIENCES

Ruangguru CAMP x Kampus Merdeka (Study Independent)

Frontend Engineer

(August 2022 - December 2022)

Learn about building a frontend on a website using the React JS framework in five months. In this program, I had the opportunity to gain a lot of knowledge and assignments starting from basic to advanced programming such as using React JS and APIs.

DS Akademik (Volunteer)

IT Division

(September 2020 - December 2022)

- Responsible for administering the website used for online trial advice, as well as those related to computing systems and networks.
- Responsible for the implementation of online mentoring every two weeks
- Do website development and resolve errors

National Competition UI / UX DIMAS TI 2022

Design UI/UX

(June 2022 - June 2022)

In this competition my team and I won second place at the national level UI / UX design DIMAS-TI AMLI 2022. This competition was organized by the Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences (UNNES) in collaboration with the Indonesian LPTK MIPA Association (AMLI). The mobile application that we have designed is called Ro-BRT which is an application to integrate BRT and Buses in Indonesia. This UI/UX design competition is oriented towards product convenience and comfort from the user's point of view.

Sagara Technology (Internship)

Front End Engineering

(March 2022 - June 2022)

Within the company, I collaborated with the team to create a community platform website, which would be a place for users to share information, either chat and images. I was given a role on the front end, specifically in creating logins and uploading cv pages. I created it using the NextJS framework and styled it with Material UI.

BuildWith Angga (Bootcamp)

Full Stack Java Script Developer

(March 2022 - April 2022)

During in the Bootcamp, I learned more about Javascript and how to create a website with MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, and Node). While React JS is used on the frontend, MongoDB is used for database storage, and Express JS is used on the backend.

Himpunan Mahasiswa Ilmu Komputer UNNES 2021 (Organization)

The Staff of Economy and Creative Division

(January 2021 - December 2021)

In this organization, I am responsible for expanding HIMA's cash finances through online platforms, specifically Instagram. I was successful in raising Rp 1,500,000 as even the coordinator of online fundraising during my period there.

KMMI Technopreneur Kampus Merdeka (Short Course)

Participant

(July 2021 - October 2021)

Learning about entrepreneur who used technology to improve the future economy. In this course, I learned a lot about technopreneur, including mindset development, business strategy, digital marketing, business planning, and e-business.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS NEGERI SEMARANG

(August 2020 - Present)

Bachelor`s Informatics Engineering

3.86 from 4.0

- Create a website project using HTML, CSS, Sass and Java Script in Interaksi Manusia dan Komputer courses
- Create a website project using Laravel 8 in Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak courses
- 2nd place in UI/UX competition DIMAS-TI UNNES 2022

SMA N 1 BAE KUDUS

(June 2017 - June 2020)

High School Mathematic and Science

3.5 from 4.0

PROJECTS

Conference Paper

https://conference-paper.vercel.app/

(July 2022 - December 2022)

Conference paper is a website that is used to organize seminar paper activities. In making this website I did several things such as designing and interpreting the display into coding, slicing, adding features, and helping the backend in database design. In designing the display using tools Figma. This website is built using Next JS, Bootstrap CSS, Express JS, Node JS, and Mongo DB as the database

DS Sukses Akademik

http://dipo-sri.my.id/

(September 2020 - December 2022)

DS Academic Success is a program presented to assist high school students in preparing for further studies. DS Success Academic has an active website with several features such as an academic and officer e-sisfo system that displays user information in it. As well as the e-CBT system, which is an online exam system that will display student scores at the end. With regard to the website, I am responsible for maintenance, adding website features, monitoring during online exams, and matters related to computing systems and networks.

SIAAP (Sistem Informasi Akademik dan Pembayaran)

https://siaap-school-project-lita15.vercel.app/

(June 2022 - July 2022)

SIAAP is a website for Junior High Schools that focuses on academic information systems and payment management. Students, teachers, and administrators all have roles on the website. The website offers personal information, a routine agenda or schedule, report cards, grade input, administration, and school information. I used Next JS and Bootstrap framework to create it.

RoBRT (Resourceful Online BRT)

(April 2022 - June 2022)

https://www.figma.com/proto/SVyeT8gifVop5PzrenIzXM/RoBRT?node-id=452%3A2962&scaling=scale-down&starting-point-node-id=332%3A158

RoBRT is a mobile application that helps the user in ordering and paying for BRT and Buses online, as well as providing real-time maps to user points, directions to the nearest bus stops and travel estimates, integration of BRT and Buses in Indonesia, and can find out the contents and crowd of passengers and buses. I collaborated with the team from the preparation of user proposals until the testing stage. I used the Figma application to make it.

SKILLS

Design (Figma), Basic Programming (C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript), Data Analyst (Pyhton), Database (MySQL, MongoDB), Framework (Bootstrap CSS, Tailwind CSS, , Material UI, Laravel 8, Express JS, React JS, Node JS, Next JS).